MARCOS LÓPEZ SAPITRI CV



CONTACT

-Email: marcoslopezsapitri.123@gmail.com -Phone number/WhatsApp :+31627424260 -Instagram: @marcoslasaye -Facebook: Marcos López Sapitri

INTRODUCTION

My name is Marcos Lopez Sapitri, I'm Spanish-Indonesian, Male, I'm 27 years old and I have full availability to work now.

My work experience is wide: Social Media Management, SEO Marketing, AI Image processing, Tourism, Hospitality, Logistics, Public Relations, Events Organizer... Although I'm always ready and excited to accept new challenges.

Able to talk fluently in 4 languages: Spanish, English, Indonesian and Javanese... Also I can hold my own in French, Italian and Portuguese.

EXPERIENCE

Blue Coral Homestay, Karimunjawa, Indonesia- *General Manager & Tour Coordinator*April 2018-December 2020

M.R.X Group (Freelance), Jakarta, Ind- Event Organizer

October 2018- February 2019

Freelance, Karimunjawa, Ind- Martial Arts Trainer/Coach
June 2020- September 2020

Big K Hostel, Karimunjawa, Ind- SEO Marketing(Morning Shift) - F&B Department manager (Afternoon Shift)

September 2020-December 2020

Jepara Garden Resort, Jepara, Ind- Operational & Staff Manager & Supervisor
February 2021- April 2021

Ingram Micro Commerce & Lifecycle Services (de Bijenkorf), Tilburg, The Netherlands- Smart Inbound/Picking/Shop Vas Warehouse Operator

May 2021- October 2021

DSV Solutions Roosendaal (Primark), Roosendaal, NL - *Warehouse Employee (Inbound)*October 2021- December 2021

Kuehne+Nagel B.V. Zaandam, NL - *Warehouse Employee*April 2022 - December 2022

Locca Sea House, Bali, Indonesia - PR & Promotor
January – February 2023

Kuehne+Nagel B.V., **Zaandam, NL** - *Warehouse Operator*May - June 2023

Rhenus Warehousing Solutions Eindhoven B.V., Eindhoven, NL - Warehouse Employee
June - October 2023

Yonaguni Fiesta, Bali, Indonesia – Event Organizer
November 2023

Bamboo Oasis Resort, Bali, Indonesia – Marketing & Public Relations

April - Actual 2023

EDUCATION

IES Adeje , Spain - High School Certificate

May 2014

HTML 5 Course - udemy.com / Teacher : Víctor Robles February 2023

SEO and WEB Positioning Course – udemy.com / Teacher: Jorge Jaramillo
January 2024

Excel (Microsoft) complete course – *udemy.com / Teacher: Miguel Maraby*June 2021

CSS and CSS3 standard: Responsive, SASS, Flexbox, Grid and Bootstrap -

udemy.com / Teacher: Víctor Robles

March 2024

Marketing Strategies and Digital Marketing – udemy.com / Teacher: Andres Brachetta & Belén
Rodríguez

March 2024

SKILLS / ABILITIES

- MARKETING STRATEGIES (MARKETING MIX, SMART OBJECTIVES, AIDA METHOD, ETC...)
- KEYWORDS ANALYSIS AND STRATEGY (SHORT-TAIL, LONG-TAIL)
- SEO AND WEB POSITIONING SPECIALIST (GOOGLE ALGORITM, SITEMAPS, AMP LANDING PAGES ETC...)
- SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING (INSTAGRAM, FACEBOOK, YOUTUBE, ETC...)
- HTML 5 (UPDATED STANDARD AND SEO ORIENTED)
- CSS3: RESPONSIVE DESIGN, SASS, FLEXBOX, GRID, BOOTSTRAP
- EXCEL/SHEETS, WORD/DOCS, POWERPOINT/SLIDES (MICROSOFT AND GOOGLE)
- CANVA (SOCIAL MEDIA POSTS, LOGOS, VIDEO EDITING)
- MICROSOFT CLIPCHAMP AND CAPCUT (VIDEO EDITING)
- OTA (ONLINE TRAVEL AGENT)
- GOOGLE COLLAB and STABLE DIFUSSION XL (AI IMAGE PROCESSING AND OTHER APPS)
- GOOGLE TRENDS & GOOGLE ANALYTICS
- NOTION AND GOOGLE CALENDAR (PLANNING AND ORGANIZING EVENTS, MEETINGS,ETC...)
- LANGUAGES: SPANISH, ENGLISH, INDONESIAN